schoolwebpages.com 2011-05-19

# Privacy Policy - THiNQ Ed

Visitors to THiNQ Ed's website are not required to provide personal information. If you request information or forms from us we ask for information such as your name, address, email address, district, school, and title. Any information collected from you for such purposes is voluntary.

THiNQ Ed is required to collect personal information about you when you register on our website. We need information such as your name, address, email address, district/school and credit card information in order to fulfill certain online transactions. THiNQ Ed may also use that information to contact you about other information, services or products related to the your purchase in which you might be interested. Only you can make changes to your personal information. If you would like to correct any information that has been inaccurately provided to us or that has changed, or to delete your name and other personal information please select the "Contact Us" button of the appropriate THiNQ Ed page and send us clear instructions to that effect.

Upon registration, you will be provided with your logon information with which you can access your profile and/or community sites. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your personal logon information, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur with respect to your personal logon information. You agree to immediately notify THiNQ Ed of any unauthorized use of your personal logon information

Because our online services are offered in conjunction with the services of other companies such as network broadband providers, virus protection, and other services necessary to run the business, THiNQ Ed will be sharing your information with those companies. We share the following information: Name, address, phone, school/district, and/or email to properly service you and/or reach you in event of issues. See Terms of Service - Privacy Policy, and Terms of Service - Sale or Distribution of Information.

If THiNQ Ed believes that you are violating THiNQ Ed's Terms of Service or are causing injury through interference or otherwise, THiNQ Ed will disclose personal information necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action, or when THiNQ Ed is legally required to disclose such information.

THiNQ Ed's website does contain links to other websites that may collect personal information about you, and we have no control over the privacy issues of those websites. You must contact such websites for their own privacy policies, if any. See Terms of Service regarding Links/Third Party Websites.

When you provide us with credit card information in order to complete a purchase transaction or for verification purposes, we transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format. We use industry-standard, SSL (secure socket layer) encryption. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and so we can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

When children under the age of 13 attempt to register with THiNQ Ed, we ask for a parent or guardian to provide consent before we collect any registration information. Children should always ask a parent for permission before sending personal information to anyone online. Any privacy policy changes will be posted here. Questions regarding THiNQ Ed's privacy statement can be directed to [info@THiNQEd.com.](mailto:info@thinqed.com)

© 2009 THiNQ Ed
